i'm able to adapt to whatever position
我能够适应任何姿势
that needs to be done and and in this
我有能力适应任何位置 需要做和做
需要这样做和这样做,以及在这方面
that needs to be done and and in this
case understanding how great Luca is how
需要这样做,并在此情况下理解卢卡有多伟大
了解卢卡有多伟大
case understanding how great Luca is how
on the rise Austin is I'mma pick you
了解卢卡有多伟大 如何升起奥斯汀 我选择你
升起奥斯汀是我要选你
on the rise Austin is I'mma pick you
apart you know instead of always having
奥斯汀升起 是因为我要把你分开 你知道,而不是总是有
你们知道的,而不是永远知道的,
apart you know instead of always having
to be at the head of the at at the head
而不是总是坐在头部的头部
坐在头部 头部 头部 头部
to be at the head of the at at the head
of the of the play now all eyes are on
站在戏头头 站在戏头 眼都睁着
众目所见,
of the of the play now all eyes are on
me and it's a five on five game you know
现在所有的眼睛都盯着我 这是五对五的游戏,你知道
我和它是一个五对五的游戏 你知道
me and it's a five on five game you know
or you know being you know with Luca's
我和它的五对五 5游戏你知道或你知道你知道 你了解与卢卡的
或者你知道自己知道 与卢卡的
or you know being you know with Luca's
ability to Yeah to to manipulate a
或者你知道自己知道 卢卡有能力
a 能够使用
ability to Yeah to to manipulate a
defense scoring the defense yeah if you
有能力使用能力来操纵 操纵国防的辩护评分
辩方的国防评分 对,如果你
defense scoring the defense yeah if you
put two on him and and now when the ball
如果你给他打两拳 现在当球打球时
给他两下,当球响起时,
put two on him and and now when the ball
is swung to me and I'm going against a
给他两下,现在,当球 向我挥舞,我要去对抗一个
对我一挥一挥,我就要对抗
is swung to me and I'm going against a
closeout which is h it doesn't happen to
对我挥棒,我反对关闭 这是H它不会发生
关闭,这是h 它不会发生
closeout which is h it doesn't happen to
much you know in my career stay home for
在我的职业生涯中 你知道的不多 留在家里
在我的职业生涯中,你知道的很多 留在家里
much you know in my career stay home for
22 years for 22 years to to get eyes on
你知道在我的职业生涯中 22年呆在家里22年 22年,看一眼
22年 22年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年
22 years for 22 years to to get eyes on
someone else for a change and then I'm
22年 22年 22 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 年 22 22 年 22 年 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22 22
换换人换换人,然后我
someone else for a change and then I'm
catching on the backside with a live
换一个人换换换人 然后我就跟活人 一起在背面追着生活
与活生生的在背上捕捉
catching on the backside with a live
dribble or I'm cutting through traffic
背对着一条活生生的流水 或我截断交通堵塞
要不然我就切断交通
dribble or I'm cutting through traffic
you know it it's but like one of the
或我切断交通... ...你知道的... ...但就像...
你知道,它只是它,但像其中之一
you know it it's but like one of the
highest forms of intelligence is also
你知道,这是它,但就像 最高的一种 情报形式也是
最高情报形式也是最高情报形式
highest forms of intelligence is also
knowing what your sacrifice needs to be
最高智商形式 也是知道你们需要牺牲什么
本字幕由AI大模型生成